Help me!
救救我
Can you play at peek-a-boo?
你能玩藏貓貓嗎
I can play at peek-a-boo!
我能玩藏貓貓
Can you see me? Yes, I can.
你能看見我嗎 是的 我能
Peek-a-peek-a-peek-a-peek-a-boo!
藏貓 藏貓 藏貓貓
Well done. That's very good. Now, ssh!
做得好 非常棒 現在 噓
Still.
坐好
And everyone up.
大家起立
And that's the end of the week. Well done.
這周的課結束 好樣的
- Hey.
- 嘿
Sorry.
抱歉
Kat's boyfriend is taking her to Paris for the weekend
凱特的男朋友帶她去巴黎過週末
and mine is taking me to a disused quarry!
我男朋友卻帶我去廢棄的獵場
It's a flooded quarry. Trust me. It's lovely.
是個被淹沒的獵場 相信我 很可愛
It's the last chance to see it
在開發商把那建上樓前
before the developers build over it.
這是最後一次機會了
'Speed camera ahead.'
前方有測速攝像頭
- Good on you, Kylie. - You're such a boy!
- 好樣的 凱麗 - 你真是個孩子
And I can mate it up to my mobile phone. Pretty sexy, huh?
這點可以用我的手機來彌補 它很性感吧
Stop it, I'm driving.
停下 我在開車呢
What's that?
那是什麼
The guy's wife had a bad back. Kinky, huh?
這傢伙的老婆背不好 很奇怪對吧
Actually, it's quite nice.
事實上 挺舒服的
Do you want me to pull over?
你想讓我停車嗎
'Good afternoon. You've been talking about fining parents
下午好 你一直在談無力的家長
'who fail to control their children's behaviour.
他們不能控制自己孩子的行為
'When was the policy introduced? '
這種政策什麼時候實行的
'As you probably remember The Respect Agenda
學會尊重是05年大選
was a big issue in the last election at 2005.
的重要議題
'Tony Blair wanted to bring back a sense of respect
布萊爾想把尊重的思想
'in schools and communities.'
帶入學校與社區
'So increase the amount of support for parents,
所以提高給家長的資助
'including parenting contracts,
包括與家長簽訂合同
'to get parents to attend parenting classes.'
讓家長去參加如何為人父母的課程
'It's a case of... "It's your problem, you sort it."
這個問題是… 這是你的問題 你來解決
'It's hard to do without the school behind you.
沒有學校支持 這難以做到
'...struggling to school as well
…不願去學校
'I have an 8-year-old struggling to school as well.'
我家的8歲孩子也不願去學校
'Get your kids to school This is a tiny minority and
讓你的孩子去上學 這是少數人的做法
children need to be in school in order to learn,
孩子需要學東西
that is crucial.
這很關鍵
'However, the early intervention isn't as quick to... '
然而 早期的干預不夠迅速來…
'It's hard to turn it over, being fined.
這種被處罰的局面很難被扭轉
Kids are not learning anything by that.
孩子們從中學不到任何東西
'They know we're going to pay so they gonna mention it.
他們知道我們會付錢的 所以他們會提起
They find it hilarious.
他們覺得很高興
'You know, reading about themselves in the papers... '
在報紙上讀到他們…
It's up here somewhere.
就在這附近
'At the traffic lights, turn left.'
在十字路口處左轉
Jesus!
上帝啊
Here it is. Beer, bed and breakfast.
到了 有啤酒 床和早餐
Perfect.
太好了
No way!
不是吧
Excuse me?
抱歉
Great bar presence!
酒吧的氣氛不錯
Ey up, me duck?
要點什麼
Two pints of lager, please.
請來兩品脫啤酒
Give it back, give it back, give it back!
還給我 還給我 還給我
A bit past their bedtime, isn't it?
他們應該上床了 對吧
Yeah, poor things must be exhausted.
是的 小東西們一定累壞了
That child needs a good...
小孩需要個好的…
I bloody told you!
我他媽告訴你了
Another pint of Wife-Beater?
再來一點嗎
Yep.
好的
- Call yourself a mother? - You what?
- 你就怎麼當媽媽的 - 你怎麼
You want beef, eh? You want beef?
你想要牛肉嗎 你想要牛肉嗎
You fucking dickhead! You want beef?
你這個小雜種 你想要牛肉嗎
- Go and tell them to shut up. - You tell them.
- 去告訴他們閉嘴 - 你去說
What are you? A man or a mouse?
你是什麼 男人還是老鼠
Look, it was all right the last time I was here.
聽著 我上次來還挺好的
Pissed up with your dive buddies?
跟你的潛水器具一起被氣死了嗎
I promise you, the quarry's fucking stunning.
我向你保證 那他媽的獵場很好
The quarry's stunning.
獵場很好
No "fucking".
別說粗話
Please, Miss?
拜託 小姐
'At your first opportunity, turn left.'
一有路口就左轉
Eden Lake, my arse! Slapton Quarry!
伊甸湖 他媽的 斯萊普頓獵場
"Gated community"? Who are they so afraid of?
"設柵欄區域" 他們害怕誰
Everyone.
每個人
This is getting more and more romantic.
越來越浪漫了
You've brought me to a building site!
你帶我到了建築工地
Look, will you just trust me?
聽著 你相信我好嗎
This used to be a public park. Look at this.
這兒以前是公共公園 看這兒
Here we go.
我們到了
'At your first opportunity, turn around.'
有機會就掉頭
Oh, ye of little faith!
有點信仰好不好
What do you think?
你怎麼想
It's beautiful.
很漂亮
I can see it.
我看得出來
- Hello. - Hey!
- 你好 - 嘿
- Have you cycled all the way here? - And no Kylie!
- 你是騎自行車來的？ - 沒有凱麗的指導
What have you got there? A caterpillar?
你騎的什麼車 履帶式嗎
My mum says I shouldn't talk to strangers.
我媽媽說不要跟陌生人說話
Your mum's quite right. We'll leave you to it.
你媽媽說得對 我們走吧
Come on.
來
Yes, you see, it is missing 50 executive homes.
是的 你看 這兒少了50座房子
I love it.
我喜歡這兒
Is that new?
這是新的嗎
Yeah. Do you like it?
是的 你喜歡嗎
I like the bottom. I'm not so sure about the top, though.
我喜歡底褲 我不確定上面怎樣
- What the fuck are you doing here? - Clear off!
- 你他媽的在這兒幹嘛 - 滾開
- What the fuck's all this shit? - Fucking little prick.
- 這是怎麼回事 - 該死的小雜種
Hey, that's the little boy we saw.
嘿 是我們看到的那個小男孩
Since when did you support England?
你什麼時候支持英格蘭隊了
Little hoods.
小傻逼
Here, Mark, watch this.
這個 馬克 看
Oh, Steve...
史蒂夫
It's just boys being boys.
只是男孩逞能而已
As long as they leave us alone.
只要他們別煩我們就好
Run for it, run!
快跑
- Get the fuck out of here! - Go on, have him.
- 媽的 給我滾 - 去抓住他
Jesus!
上帝啊
Bonnie, come!
邦妮 來
Oh, my God.
我的天哪
Good girl, good girl, good girl.
好丫頭 好丫頭
Come on then.
來
Lovely.
挺好
Fancy a dip before it craps in the water?
想在它把水弄髒之前去泡一泡嗎
No, you go. I'll keep an eye on the stuff.
不 你去 我看著東西
Probably not a bad idea.
也許是個好主意
Good girl.
好丫頭
Oh, man!
哦 夥計
Come on, Bonnie! Bonnie!
來 邦妮
Bonnie, come here, girl! Come here! Come here!
邦妮 過來 丫頭 過來
Good girl, Bonnie.
好丫頭 邦妮
Hey, guys. Can you do us a favour and turn the music down?
夥計們 能幫我們個忙把音樂關小嗎
- Can't hear you, mate. - Turn your sounds down.
- 聽不見你 夥計 - 把音量關小
Can't hear you, mate.
聽不見 夥計
- What are you doing? - And watch your dog.
- 你在做什麼 - 看好你的狗
- He's scaring my girlfriend. - She.
- 他嚇著我女朋友了 - 是她
Bitch. She's a bitch.
賤人 她是個賤人
Come on, guys. Don't be dicks. This is a big beach.
別跟傻逼似的 海灘很大
There's room for all of us.
有足夠的空間給每個人
Who are you calling a dick?
你叫誰傻逼
And what are you looking at? My tits?
你在看什麼 我的奶頭嗎
Fucking jog on! Prick.
媽的滾一邊去 瘋子
Dickhead.
畜生
Hey, what a prick!
嘿 真是個瘋子
Mug!
媽的
Why don't we just find another spot?
我們為什麼不再找個地方呢
I won't be bullied by a bunch of 12-year-olds.
我不能被一群12歲的小孩嚇住了
And let it ruin our afternoon?
那就讓這事毀了我們的下午？
We were here first.
我們先來的
Well, this is relaxing
這就讓人舒心了
- What are you doing? - Fuck off!
- 你在做什麼 - 滾開
Why? Why?
為什麼 為什麼
Oh, mate, I love bird-watching.
夥計 我喜歡偷窺
- What's with you, you tit? - You're the tit!
- 你喜歡什麼 奶頭嗎 - 奶頭是你
What are you looking at her for?
你看她幹什麼
I'm not looking at her face, just her tits.
我沒看她的臉 看她的奶頭
She's an ugly bint.
她是個丑婊子
Yeah, do you want my autograph?
是的 想要我簽名嗎
Happy now? Hmm?
現在開心了嗎
Hey, Jenny!
嘿 珍妮
Nearly!
快了
Fancy another brewski?
想再喝點啤酒嗎
Yeah, why not?
是的 為什麼不呢
Steve, what's that?
史蒂夫 那是什麼
It's nothing.
沒什麼
There's not much to do after dark.
天黑後沒什麼可做
Nope.
是的
Wanna check out our exclusive New England home?
想看看專屬於我們的新英格蘭之家嗎
Sure.
當然
- Do you like it? - I think it's beautiful.
- 你喜歡嗎 - 我覺得很漂亮
Stephen Taylor...
史蒂芬·泰勒
What's that noise?
那是什麼聲音
It's just the wind.
風聲而已
No, that's not the wind.
不 不是風聲
Could be a fox.
可能是狐貍
Or a donkey.
或者驢子
No, listen. Ssh!
不 聽著 噓
You're just imagining it.
是你的想像
- I'll go take a look. - No, don't go... Go.
- 我去看看 - 不 別走 去吧
Steve?
史蒂夫
Hello?
有人嗎
Steve, stop messing around!
史蒂夫 別添亂了
Steve!
史蒂夫
- That was horrible. - I'm sorry.
- 嚇死我了 - 抱歉
- Get off! - I'm really sorry.
- 走開 - 真對不起
- Ow! You're freezing! - Then warm me up.
- 你凍透了 - 那就暖暖我
You're a big, crude, pikey oaf!
你就是個愛爾蘭大大大傻子
I love you. Love you.
我愛你 愛你
I am absolutely starving.
我真的快餓死了
- I could eat a horse. - So move to France.
- 我可以吃下一匹馬 - 那就去法國吧
Fuck!
我操
Shit!
媽的
- What's happened? - Little fuckers!
- 怎麼了 - 小雜種們
- How's your tyre, mate? - Fucking git!
- 你的輪胎怎麼樣 夥計 - 滾一邊去
Little fuckers!
小雜種們
No, wait, Steve!
不 等等 史蒂夫
- Watch it! - Shit!
- 當心 - 媽的
You should've got a smaller body, fucking dollar boy!
你塊頭應該小點 該死的蠢蛋
- Breakfast? - Fuck!
- 要吃早飯嗎 - 我操
Right, what would you like?
好的 你想要什麼
The full English with white toast and coffee. Thanks.
全套英國早餐 加白吐司和咖啡 謝謝
- And for you? - I'll get the same.
- 你呢 - 一樣的
Hey, you wouldn't have seen a bunch of kids
你有沒有見到一群
tooling around on BMXs, would you?
騎自行車的孩子
Certainly have. Been terrorising you?
當然了 他們煩到你了嗎
- Well, hassling us. - Little terrors.
- 是騷擾我們 - 小恐怖份子
I wouldn't worry too much, a big boy like you.
你這樣的大男孩 不必擔心的
They punctured my back tyre.
他們戳破了我的後輪胎
I thought parents might want to know.
我想應該告訴父母
Not my kids.
不是我的孩子
No, I didn't mean they were your kids.
不 我不是說他們是你的孩子
Not mine.
不是我的
Never mind.
算了
I don't want any trouble.
我不想惹麻煩
Making friends?
你在交朋友嗎
I think she likes me.
我想她喜歡我
What the?
怎麼回事
No, Steve, it's not worth it.
別 史蒂夫 這沒必要
If everyone said that, where would we be?
如果人人都這麼說 我們的處境會怎樣
I'll be back in a minute.
我一會兒回來
Hello?
有人嗎
Anyone home?
有人在家嗎
- Come on, you're blocking my drive! - OK.
- 快開走 你擋我道了 - 好的
- Come on! - All right!
- 快點
Sorry!
抱歉
Stupid bitch!
蠢婊子
Shit!
媽的
Brett! Is that you? Get down here now!
布萊特 是你嗎 現在就給我下來
Can't run away, little bunny.
你跑不了的 小兔子
Yeah, that's right, you can't because you're in a box.
是的 你跑不出來因為你在籠子
Brett! Brett, don't make me come up there!
布萊特 別讓我上去
Shit!
媽的
Brett!
布萊特
The hutch should be destroyed. Burn it.
應該把籠子毀了 燒了它
Let's go!
我們走
I can feel that schoolteacher look.
我能感到你又像老師一樣看我了
Yeah, you're lucky. You could have broken something.
是的 你很幸運 你可能弄壞什麼東西的
- Let's just enjoy the weekend. - Yeah, I'd like that.
- 我們享受週末吧 - 好的 我喜歡
Yes?
好嗎
- You were going to say something? - No, not a word.
- 你不要說點什麼嗎 - 一句也沒
- Are you sure? - Yeah, I'm sure.
- 你確定嗎 - 是的 我確定
Because I thought you were looking at my foot.
因為我想你在看我的腳
No, wait. No, no!
不 等等 不要
You're going in!        Steve, no!
- 你要進去了 - 史蒂夫 別
No!
不要
- Oh, it's fucking freezing. - Language!
- 真他媽的冷 - 注意語言
All right, lazy bones?
好嗎 懶蟲
It's amazing the stuff you find at the bottom of the lake.
在湖底能找到這種東西真驚人
Steve, where's the beach bag?
史蒂夫 海灘包在哪兒
It was right here.
就在這兒
I don't believe it. It's got the car keys in it.
不敢相信 車鑰匙在堶
Please, God, don't tell me...
上帝啊 請別告訴我
Fuck!
我操
Tossers!
雜種
- Are you OK? - Yeah.
- 你還好嗎 - 是的
Jenny, come on.
珍妮 快點
Come on.        No... Let's just leave it.
- 拜託 - 不 我們別管了
They've got our car.
車在他們那兒
Go on, go on. Go on!
來啊來啊
Fucking shitting itself! Fuck off!
該死的混帳 滾開
Brett!
布萊特
Listen... I don't care what you're up to here.
聽著 我不管你們要在這兒幹什麼
I just want my car back.
我只想要回我的車
It's not us, mate.
不是我們幹的 夥計
Car keys, phone, wallet.
車鑰匙 手機 錢包
- Not us, mate. - Steve, come on. Let's leave it.
- 不是我們 夥計 - 史蒂夫 得了 別管了
- You're wearing my shades. - They're mine, mate.
- 你戴著我的墨鏡 - 是我的 夥計
Your Ray-Ban Aviators?
你的雷凡飛行鏡嗎
Fakes, mate.
假的 夥計
Yeah, Steve, come on.
是的 史蒂夫 算了
Listen... You've had your fun.
聽著 你們已經玩夠了
Let's just call it quits. Tell me where the car is.
我們就此作罷 告訴我車在哪兒
Keep that animal back.
讓那畜生退後
- Where's my fucking car? - I've got no idea, mate.
- 我的車在哪兒 - 我不知道 夥計
- Watch that fucking dog! - Watch yours!
看住你的瘋狗     看住你的
What did you say?
你說什麼
That's my phone.
那是我的手機
- Steve... - Got the same ringtone as me?
- 史蒂夫 - 你手機鈴聲也跟我一樣嗎
Steve!
史蒂夫
Hit him! He's got a fucking knife!
打他 他有把刀
Bonnie...
邦妮
Bonnie! Bonnie!
邦妮 邦妮
You stuck my dog.
你捅死了我的狗
It was an accident. Give me the car keys.
這是意外 給我車鑰匙
I'll drive her to the vet.
我送她去看獸醫
Come on, let's go.
得了 走吧
Fuck off!
滾開
She's... She's fucking dying.
她 她要死了
I'm sorry.
對不起
- She's fucking dying! - Brett...
- 她要死了 - 布萊特
- Fuck off!
- 滾開
Bonnie, don't die on me. Not you. Bonnie!
邦妮 別離開我 不要 邦妮
Steve...
史蒂夫
I've got the car keys. Let's just go.
我拿到鑰匙了 快走
- Come on! - Don't die on me, Bonnie!
- 得了 - 別離開我 邦妮
Come on, Steve!
得了 史蒂夫
Bonnie!
邦妮
Come on, come on.
快點 快點
Get 'em!
抓住他們
Fuck!
我操
Steve, quick!
史蒂夫 快點
Right!
好的
Shit!
媽的
Go back!
快倒回去
- Get on to it! - Jesus Christ!
- 上去 - 上帝啊
Come on!
快點
Quick, go back!
快倒車
Get out the fucking car!
給我下車
- Oh, my God, oh, my God! - Fuck!
- 我的上帝 上帝啊 - 我操
Get out the fucking car!
給我下車
Fucking prick!
該死的雜種
Oh, my God! Shit!
我的天哪 媽的
You fucking bitch!      Steve!
- 你這個臭婊子 - 史蒂夫
I can't see, I can't fucking see.
我看不見 媽的我什麼都看不見
I can't see where we're fucking going! Jesus Christ!
媽的我看不見前面的路 上帝啊
Shit!
媽的
Are you all right? Wait.
你沒事吧 等等
- I can't get... - I'm stuck!
- 我找不到… - 我被卡住了
I'm fucking stuck!
我他媽被卡住了
- Wait. - Jesus!
- 等等 - 上帝啊
- I can't get it. - OK... Listen to me.
- 我找不到 - 好的 聽我說
- Oh, my God, they're coming! - Listen to me!
- 我的天哪 他們來了     3 - 聽我說
Listen. Go. Find a road. Take this.
聽著 快跑 找條路 拿著這個
- No... - Go get help! Go!
- 不要 - 去找人幫忙 快跑
Fucking kill 'em!
宰了他們
This way, this way, come on!
這邊 這邊 快點
Brett, it's over here!
布萊特 在這兒
Fuck!
我操
Come over here. I've got the car!
過來 我找到車了
Brett, this is fucked up!
布萊特 搞砸了
It's ten fucking miles into town in the dark.
現在是晚上 到城埵10英里
She's not fucking Lassie! It's out of the time, blood man.
她又不是小姑娘 快沒時間了
Are you watching the road?
你在看路嗎
No one goes home. You get here now!
誰都不准回家 你給我過來
Please, let me go. I won't say anything. Please, let me go.
放了我 我什麼也不會說的 拜託 放了我
Listen, Brett, people know that we're here.
聽著 布萊特 朋友都知道我們在這
They're going to call the police.
他們會報警的
If you let me go, I swear on my life, I won't tell anyone.
如果放了我 我發誓 我不會告訴任何人的
Look, guys, come on, please.
聽著 夥計們 求你們了
We can stop this. Nobody's died yet.
我們可以停止的 目前還沒有人死
My fucking dog died though!
但我的狗死了
I'm sorry. It was an accident.
抱歉 那是意外
It was an accident.
那是意外
There's going to be another accident
等我找到你的賤人
when I find that bitch of yours!
會再發生一起意外的
"No one's died." Wait and see what happens to her
"還沒有人死" 等到我看到她
when I fucking see her!
等著瞧她會怎樣
Get the fuck off me! Fucking little prick!
媽的放開我 小兔崽子
Let's not be head-loose, right?
別衝動 好嗎
- Who are you calling head-loose? - Let's not be rash.
- 你說誰衝動 - 我們別急
First phone he sees, 999 - who's fucking head-loose?
他看到的第一個電話 110 是誰衝動
No, this is rash shit, man. I never touched him.
不 這是胡扯 我從沒碰過他
- What, you didn't touch him? - No, mate.
- 怎麼 你沒碰他 - 是的 夥計
You fucking touch him now then!
那你現在就碰
Him or me.
他或者我
You wanna front, you wanna act like the fucking big man?
你想上前 表現得像個男人樣嗎
You'll step up now.
現在就上
All right.
好的
Jesus...
上帝啊
Paige, get this!
佩吉 拿著這個
Don't fucking record it, man.
媽的別拍下來 夥計
No, wait.
不要 等等
Fucking wait!
媽的等等
- Go on then. - Fuck you!
- 現在就去 - 你去死吧
No. That's not even a proper cut. Deeper.
不 還不夠 割得再深一點
Deeper!
深一點
Fuck!
我操
All right, now everyone'll have a dig. Marky Mark?
好的 現在 每人來一刀 馬奇·馬克
Jesus!
上帝啊
- Oh, man, I can't fucking see this! - Jesus!
- 夥計 我見不了這場面 - 上帝啊
- Fuck's sake. - Go on, Mark.
- 真他媽的 - 快上 馬克
Jesus Christ, fucking bollocks.
上帝啊 該死的雜種
Ricky Dicky...
堜_·迪奇
Go on.
來吧
Shit! My shoe!
媽的 我的鞋子
These are fucking Gold Tops, man. Brand-new.
有金邊的呢 夥計 新的
You little fuckwit.
你這個小雜種
Cooper! Bang on, mate, you're up!
庫珀 來吧 夥計 到你了
What?
怎麼
Come on, mate.
來吧 夥計
Knife.
刀子
Paige, keep that phone up.
佩吉 都拍下來
Right, Coops, everyone has a dig.
是的 每個人都來
Go on then, Cooper. Let's see your bottle.
來吧 庫珀 看你多有膽
Come on, come on. Please.
快點 快點
Brett, I can't.
布萊特 我不能
For fuck's sake, listen! We're all in this together. Go on.
看在上帝面上 聽著 我們在一條船上 快點
- Come on. He's only a little scared. - I'm not scared.
- 拜託 他很害怕 - 我才不怕
Listen. He's heard all of our fucking names.
聽著 他知道我們所有人的名字
Either do it or he's gonna spill.
不這麼做他就會報警
Go on...
快點
Do it! Cut his fucking tongue out!
快點 把他的舌頭切掉
- Fucking hell! That's bloody. - That's lethal.
- 真他媽的 是血 - 真狠
- Here you are. - I can't believe you did that.
- 給你 - 我不敢相信你做了
Look - it's Tony Montana!
看 是唐尼·馬塔那(《疤觀煞星》黑幫頭領)
All right. Now we've got to finish this.
好的 現在我們得結束這一切
Please, please...
拜託 拜託
Please, please, please.
拜託 拜託 拜託
Please...
拜託
What's up?
怎麼了
Bluetooth. She's fucking here.
藍牙 她就在這兒
Jenny, run! Run!
珍妮 快跑
Come on! Run!
快點 快跑
There's the bitch!
那賤人在那兒
Bitch!
賤人
Well, fuck the bikes. Come on!
去他媽的自行車 快點
Fuck!
我操
Get to the clearing. Guard the fucker.
到空地那去 看著那個混蛋
Right.
好的
Where is she?
她在哪兒
Oh, shit!
媽的
- Brett, he's gone! - What?
- 布萊特 他不見了 - 什麼
He's not here!
他不在這兒
Mate, he's cut to fuck. Ain't going too far. Follow the blood.
夥計 他受了傷 走不了多遠 跟著血跡走
Come on!
快點
Fuck's sake!
操他媽的
Oi! Oi!
奧依 奧依
- Steve! - Jenny...
- 史蒂夫 - 珍妮
Come on! We've got to get out of here!
快點 我們要離開這兒
Come on...
快點
This way.
這邊
Gently! All right?
慢慢躺下 好嗎
- I'm all right. - That's it.
- 我沒事 - 那就好
OK. We're going to clean you up, all right?
好的 要給你清理乾淨好嗎
We're going to clean you up.
給你清理乾淨
Drink some water.
喝點水
I'm...
我
Well done. All right.
做得好 好的
OK, this is going to sting.
好的 會很疼的
OK...
好
Well done. I know it does sting.
好樣的 我知道會很疼
- Oh, shit! - How does it look?
- 他媽的 - 看起來怎樣
- It looks worse than it is. - Let me see.
- 不如看上去那麼糟 - 讓我看看
Oh, Jesus! God! That's black blood. Gut blood.
上帝啊 是黑血 腸子堛漲
- I'm fucking bleeding to death! - You're not going to die!
- 我他媽會流血而死的 - 你不會死的
I'm not going to let you die! I'm not!
我不會讓你死的 不會的
They haven't hit any arteries.
他們沒刺中動脈
Right. You've just got to stay calm.
好的 你要冷靜下來
You have to stay calm. You can't go into shock.
冷靜 你不能激動
Deep breaths, measured breaths. Stay still.
深呼吸 慢慢來 躺好
You're going to be all right. You'll be all right,
你會沒事的 你會好起來的
you'll be OK. I promise.
沒事的 我保證
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry. I didn't know what to do.
對不起 我不知道該怎麼辦
I thought Africa for a honeymoon.
我想去非洲度蜜月
Beach first, for a rest,
先去海灘休息一下
and then safari.
接著去旅行
I don't care where we go as long as I'm with you.
只要跟你在一起 去哪兒都好
Africa sounds lovely.
非洲聽起來不錯
I even asked your old man.
我還問過你爸爸
Shit!
媽的
Other side.
另一邊
That's him. He's been here.
是他 他來過
Find him and drain him like a fucking bottle.
找到他 弄死他
- I'm tired, Brett. - Shut up, shite bag. Is that you?
- 我累了 布萊特 - 閉嘴 蠢豬 是不是
Is that you, fat lad?
是你嗎 死胖子
- No, not mine, mate. - That's a girl's footprint.
- 不 不是我的 夥計 - 那是女人的腳印
Well, she's with him, then.
那她就跟他在一起
That fucker can't be far.
那混蛋走不遠的
He's nearly half fucking dead. Listen to me. Split up.
他快死了 大家分頭找
Spread out between here and the fence. All right, come on.
在這兒和圍牆上都有血 好的 快走
You fat fuck!
你這個死胖子
Come on. Get going. Work off some of that weight, you fat shit.
快走 減減肥 你這頭豬
Sorry...
抱歉
Well done. Let's get your head down.
好樣的 把頭放低
That's it, that's it. Well done. Well done.
就是這樣 做得好
Steve?
史蒂夫
Steve! Steve, please...
史蒂夫 史蒂夫 拜託
I've got to get us out of here. OK?
我們要出去 好嗎
- I can't move. - Then I've got to go. OK?
- 我動不了 - 那我去 好嗎
I'm safe here.
我在這兒很安全
They've gone.
他們走了
You need blood, Steve, or you're going to die.
你需要血 史蒂夫 否則你會死的
I need to get to town.
我要到城堨h
I saw power pylons on the way in.
我來的時候看到有路標
They must lead somewhere.
肯定能通往城
Look.
聽著
Now you stay hidden... and you hold on.
你要藏好 要堅持住
You come back.
你會回來的
Brett, I'm really tired.
布萊特 我真的累了
Take a toke on this, you little shit!
吸口這個 你這小子
Come on!
快點
Aaaaaiee! God!
上帝啊
Oi, oi, oi! This way, yeah?
奧依 是這條路 對嗎
Come on!
快點
It's OK! It's...
沒事的
It's me. It's... It's Jenny. Remember me from the lake?
是我 我是珍妮 我們在湖邊見過的
I just... I need some help.
我 我需要幫助
I want to talk to your mum. Can you take me to her?
我要跟你媽媽談談 你能帶我去找她嗎
She's working.
她在工作
But I'm...
但我…
I really need to get into town.
我真的要進城去
Can you please just show me the way?
能拜託你帶我去嗎
Wait. Shouldn't we follow the power lines?
等等 我們為什麼不跟著路標走
No, this way's quicker.
不用 這條路快一點
My mum picks me up down here.
我媽媽來這兒接我
What? Here? In her car with your bike?
什麼 在這兒嗎 她開車載你的自行車嗎
What?
什麼
- Have you got a signal here? - No, just games.
- 在這兒有信號嗎 - 沒有 玩遊戲
She should be here soon.
她應該一會兒就來了
I thought you said your mother was working.
你不是說她在上班麼
She's finished her shift.
她剛和人換完班
- No signal? - One bar.
- 沒信號嗎 - 只有一格
- Adam, I need your phone. - Why?
- 亞當 我要用你電話 - 為什麼
- To call the police. - We shouldn't be here!
- 我要報警 - 我們不該來
- Please! - Its battery's low!
- 拜託 - 電量很低
It doesn't matter. I only need it for seconds.
沒關係 就一會
My mum might need to call me back!
我媽媽可能要打回來
Adam, your mum is coming to get you, isn't she?
亞當 你媽媽要來接你 是不是
Adam, what's going on?
亞當 怎麼回事
Where have you brought me? Please, Adam!
這兒是哪兒 請告訴我 亞當
Please... just give me the bloody phone!
拜託 把這鳥電話給我
How now brown cow!
小母牛 你好啊
She's awake! Brett, she's fucking awake!
她醒了 布萊特 她他媽的醒了
Mark, you fucking pussy! You didn't hit her hard enough!
馬克 你這個娘們 你打得不夠狠
Oh, fuck!
我操
We found him.
我們找到他了
Brett, we can't fucking do this! She's alive!
布萊特 我們不能這麼做 她還活著
And he's dead.
但他死了
We did him.
是我們幹的
Paige has got you every last one you
佩吉把你們的所為
fucking move all having a dig.
都拍下來了
It's on her phone. No ballsing out now, lads.
在她手機上 現在不能退出了 夥計們
No backing down.
沒退路了
Oh, Jesus...
上帝啊
- Paige, get filming. Come here. - Oh, fuck it!
- 佩吉 拍下來 過來 - 操他的
Look at me, man. Wanna be in our gang?
看著我 夥計 想加入我們嗎
Prove yourself, then.
那就證明你自己
No, please...! Adam, no, please... don't do it!
請不要 亞當 請別這麼做
Please, don't do it! Please...!
請不要 拜託
Go on. Go on.
快點 繼續
- What? - Listen, you've seen too much.
- 怎麼 - 聽著 你看到的太多了
You either do it now, yeah, or you're next.
你要麼下手 要麼下一個就是你
Go on, then.
那就快點
Go on!
快點
No! No-o-o!
不要
Stop!
住手
That fucking stinks.
真他媽的臭
Fucking look at that! Fucking that was you.
媽的給我看著 下手的是你
That was fucking you, not me.
是你 不是我
- Fucking you. - Please...!
- 是你 - 拜託
Fucking bitch. Ask her if it's warm.
死婊子 問她暖不暖和
Is it warm? Say it! Is it warm?
暖不暖和 說出來 暖和不
Fucking you do it an' all! Fucking you all! Ask her!
是你做的 問她
- Is it warm? Is it warm? - Say it! Louder!
- 暖和不 暖和不 - 說出來 大聲點
Is it warm?
暖和不
Fucking burn! Burn, you little bitch! Go on!
燒吧 燒死你這臭婊子 快點
Yeah! Fucking hell! Fucking smile, boy. You fucking love it.
是的 他媽的 笑吧 孩子 你喜歡的
Oi, oi!
奧依 奧依
Go on, then.
來啊
Come here, you fucking shit!
過來 你這賤人
You get the fuck back here or I'll burn him!
你要不回來我就燒死他
Come on! Come on!
快點 快點
Right! Do him!
好的 燒死他
Help! Jenny, help!
救命 珍妮 救命
Help! Help!
救命 救命
Help!
救命
- OK... - Brett, this way!
- 好的 - 布萊特 這邊
She's got the fucking map! She knows which way to go.
她有地圖 她知道路了
No, we know which way she's fucking going.
不 我們知道她要走哪條路
There's one track into town.
有條小路通到城
- She won't go far on her foot, will she? - Look.
- 她步行走不遠的 - 看
What? What does it say?
什麼 上面怎麼說
"Jenny Greengrass and Steve Taylor attacked.
珍妮·格林格拉斯和史蒂夫·泰勒被襲擊
"Mark, Brett, Ricky, Cooper."
馬克 布萊特 堜_ 庫珀
Shit, we're famous, mate!
媽的 我們出名了 夥計
- You got a match? - No, mate.
- 你有火柴嗎 - 沒有 夥計
Fuck it, then.
那就去他的
I swear. When I find that fucking bitch,
我發誓 等我找到那個賤人
I'm going to fucking bury her, mate.
我他媽要埋了她 夥計
Fucking hell!
真他媽的
Little prick, come on.
小混蛋 走
Miss...
小姐
I can't stand it...!
我受不了了
No...!
不要
No, no, no!
不 不
We're not going to fucking find her in the dark!
在夜塈畯怬鉹ㄗ鴞o
Yes, we fucking are! Go on!
是的 正是 給我繼續找
Brett!
布萊特
- Paige? - Brett!
- 佩吉 - 布萊特
Look at what you've fucking done! Fuck!
看看你他媽做了什麼 我操
You know what, Brett? Fuck this - I'm gone, mate.
你知道 布萊特 去他媽的 我要走了
What?
什麼
No. No, no, no. Paige, phone.
不不不 佩吉 電話
Look! Look, look, look. Look, look, it's you. That's you.
看哪 看看看看 是你 那是你
I didn't want this. I didn't want to fucking kill him
我不想這樣 我不想殺了他
or fucking burn that lad ever!
我不想燒死那個孩子
- And I don't want to go to pen. - Pen?
- 我也不想進監獄 - 監獄
What do you know about pen?
你知道監獄啥樣麼
Have you been inside? Has your old man been inside?
你進去過嗎 你老頭進去過嗎
What the fuck are you crying for, you fucking girl?
你他媽在哭什麼 你這娘娘腔
Who you calling?
你在打給誰
Put that down. Put that...
給我放下 給我放…
Put that down. Put it down. Put it down.
給我放下 放下 放下
Put it down.
給我放下
- Brett! - I'll fucking batter you!
- 布萊特 - 我要打死你
I'll fucking batter you!
我要打死你
Brett...!
布萊特
I... told... you... to... put... that... down!
我 告訴你 給我 放下
Fucker! Fucker! Fucker! Fucker!
混蛋 混蛋 混蛋
Turn it off. Turn it off. Turn it off.
關掉 關掉 關掉
Turn it off! Turn it off, you fucking bitch!
給我關機 關機 你這死婊子
- God! Are you OK? - You've got to help me!
- 天哪 你還好嗎 - 你要幫我
- Please, just get me out of here. - Fuck! What's going on?
- 拜託 帶我離開這兒 - 操 出什麼事了
Please, just help me. They killed my boyfriend and kill you!
求你 幫幫我 他們殺了我男朋友
Just get me out of here.
帶我離開這
All right! All right! Get in the car!
好的好的 上車
- What happened back there? - I'm being hunted.
- 發生什麼事了 - 他們在追我
- Hunted? By who? - A gang. Just get me into town.
- 追你 誰 - 一個幫派 送我進城
- Town's the other way. - Why the other way?
- 那在另一邊 - 什麼叫在另一邊
Me fucking brother's out here! He's supposed to be home.
我弟弟在這兒 他應該早回家了
- Your brother? - My little brother. Now I'm worried.
- 你弟弟？ - 我弟弟 現在我很擔心
- Oh, no... - Ricky?
- 哦不 - 堜_
Ricky, are you OK? You ready?
堜_ 你還好嗎 你準備好了嗎
I'll be there in two ticks. Yeah?
我一會兒回來 好嗎
No, please, stop! Turn around!
不要 別往這開 掉頭
- Please, go the other way! - I will.
- 請走那條路 - 我會的
Fuck! They better be OK.
我操 他們最好沒事
Ricky?
堜_
Ricky? Ricky, you little shite! Where are you?
堜_ 你這個小混蛋 你在哪兒
Little bastard! I've got better things to do.
小雜種 我還有別的事要做
Mum's worried sick.
媽媽擔心死了
This lady says she's been hunted. You know about this?
她說有人在追她 你知道這事嗎
# Please believe us We ain't ever gonna be respectable
# 請相信我 我們不會永遠被尊重 #
# Like us, hate us, but you'll... #
# 喜歡我們 討厭我們 但你會… #
Somebody, please help me!
來人哪 救救我
#... respectable, respectable... #
# 尊重 尊重 #
Don't just stand there!
別光站著
- Get her in the house. - Come on, then.
- 帶她進屋 - 那就來吧
- You've been through the wars. - What happened?
- 你的經歷很慘 - 出什麼事了
Take your time.
別急 慢慢說
Come on, give her some air.
拜託 給她點新鮮空氣
That stings, sorry. Thanks, Tan.
真臭 謝謝 唐
Yeah. We'll put this down here.
我們把她放在這兒
- You're safe now. - Lots of big ugly men around.
- 你現在安全了 - 有很多臭男人在
I'm still at Uncle Jon's.
我還在強叔叔這兒
- A woman crashed in, looking like death. - Mel!
- 有個女人衝進來 跟死了一樣 - 梅
That's a lovely ring. From your fella?
戒指挺漂亮 你男人給的嗎
What's that?
怎麼回事
Hey, Clyde! Come here! Down! Out!
嘿 克林迪 進來 低下 出去
You're breaking up. I can't hear you.
你在搗亂 我聽不見你
Sorry. He's no good with strangers.
抱歉 他對陌生人不友好
Mel? Mel, what's going on?
梅 梅 怎麼了
What the fuck?! That's Reece's van!
怎麼回事 那是堸簹漕
- Go on, tell me! - Bustard! I'll fucking kill him!
- 快點 告訴我 - 我要殺了他
- Hang on... - Give me the fucking phone!
- 等等 - 把電話給我
- Get me an ambulance. - Jon?
- 幫我叫救護車 - 強
Jon, get an ambulance. Get this lady an ambulance.
強 叫救護車 給她叫救護車
- I want the police. - Eh? No, no, no. Don't worry, love.
- 我要找警察 - 不不 別擔心 親愛的
You let us do that. Just stay here.
我們會打的 你呆在這就好
- Ssh. You just sit quiet. - I'm going to be sick.
- 你坐好了 - 我要吐了
I'll get you to the loo. Come on. Come with me. Come on, love.
我帶你去廁所 來吧 跟我走 親愛的
In here. Here we go.
在這兒 我們到了
Lee Trevitt! Get out!
李·崔維特 出去
Sorry about this.
真是抱歉
Get out! Go on, love.
出去 來吧 親愛的
Oh, God...
哦 上帝
Oh, God. Oh, God...
哦 上帝啊 上帝啊
Open the fucking door!
快點開門
Open it up!
開門
- Is this the lady? - Yeah.
- 就是她嗎 - 是的
You fucking slag! I'll fucking kill you!
你這個人渣 我要殺了你
Come on, love!
好了 親愛的
- What's he told you? He's a liar! - What about the van?!
- 他說了什麼 他是騙子 - 車是怎麼回事
I was just trying to get away. They killed Steve!
我只是想逃命 他們殺了史蒂夫
Yeah. You sell out your sick bastard boyfriend!
你背叛了你那混蛋男朋友
No. Just call the police! Call the police.
不 快報警 報警
Call the police? What good are they to her?
報警？ 他們會怎麼收拾她
Fuck!
我操
You want to play with the big boys now?
你現在想跟大男孩玩玩嗎
Jon... Jon...
強 強
She killed her little one.
她殺了她的兒子
Look at her. You fucking look at her now!
看著她 你他媽的看著她
- You fucking keep looking at her. - They're just children!
- 你他媽一直看著她 - 他們還是孩子
Just children! They're just children!
只是孩子 他們只是孩子
I didn't mean to...
我也不想的…
They started this!      And we're gonna finish it.
- 是他們挑的頭 - 那我們來結束一切
Look, there's dead kids, man.
聽著 有孩子死去了 夥計
The police will be round here. The police will ask questions.
警察會過來 他們會問起的
Doesn't mean they'll get any answers, does it?
那他們也找不到答案 不是麼
We look after our own round here.
這堿O我們說了算
- Now... Now take Brett to bed. - No...
- 現在帶布萊特去睡覺 - 不要
Brett, get upstairs now! You little bastard!
布萊特 現在上樓去 你這小雜種
Get upstairs now.
現在上樓去
Please, don't...!
請不要
Just put her in the shower.
把她放到浴缸
No-o-o!
不